Finding Aid for the Carol Burnett Papers PASC.0066
UCLA Library Special Collections
- The Carol Burnett Show (Music), Series 9.; unknown
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0112 (Box Unknown container 460 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Conductor Score. Guests: Tim Conway. Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Percussion (3 copies) Choir Electric Guitar Drums Harp Electric Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0112 (Box Unknown container 461 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Conductor Score. Guest: Tim Conway. Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums Percussion (3 copies) Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0108 (Box Unknown container 462 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Conductor Score (1 copy). Guests: Lucille Ball, Eddie Albert, Nancy Wilson. Artists: Harvey, Carol, Lucy, Vicki. Parts: Alto Sax 1 Alto Sax 2 Tenor Sax 3 Tenor Sax 4 Baritone Sax Trumpet 1 Trumpet 2 Trumpet 3 Trumpet 4 Trombone 1 Trombone 2 Trombone 3 Trombone 4 Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums Percussion (3 copies) Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 463 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Conductor Score (2 copies). Guests: Don Rickles, Mel Torme, Nanette Fabray. Artists: Carol, Mel Torme. Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Percussion (2 copies) Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0108 (Box Unknown container 464 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Conductor Score (1 copy). Guests: Lucille Ball, Eddie Albert, Nancy Wilson. Artist: Carol and Nancy. Parts: Alto Sax 1 Alto Sax 2 Tenor Sax 3 Tenor Sax 4 Baritone Sax (Bass Clarinet) Trumpet 1 Trumpet 2 Trumpet 3 Trumpet 4 Trombone 1 Trombone 2 Trombone 3 Trombone 4 Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums Percussion (2 copies) Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0121 (Box Unknown container 465 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 466 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Guests: Don Rickles, Mel Torme, Nanette Fabray Artist: Nanette Fabray Master Score, Conductor Score (2 copies) Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax 5th Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Percussion (3 copies) Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 467 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Guests: Don Rickles, Mel Torme, Nanette Fabray Parts: Drums Guitar Bass Violin #6(B) (2 copies) Piano #6 Piano "Purple Passion"
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 468 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Guests: Don Rickles, Mel Torme, Nanette Fabray Artists: Carol, Mel, Nanette, Don Master Score Conductor Score (2 copies) Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax 5th Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Drums Guitar Percussion (2 copies) Harp TACET Lead Sheet
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 469 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Guests: Don Rickles, Mel Torme, Nanette Fabray Artist: Carol Master Score Conductor Score Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax 5th Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Violin (3 copies) Cello Viola Bass Guitar Percussion (2 copies) Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 470 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Guests: Don Rickles, Mel Torme, Nanette Fabray Master Score Parts: Alto Sax 1 & 2 TACET Tenor Sax 3 & 4 TACET Baritone Sax TACET Trumpet 1-4 TACET Trombone 1-4 TACET Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Percussion TACET Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 471 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Guests: Don Rickles, Mel Torme, Nanette Fabray Master Score Parts: All Saxes TACET Trumpets TACET Trombones TACET Violins (4 copies - One for booth) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Percussion TACET Drums TACET Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 472 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 473 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Guests: Don Rickles, Mel Torme, Nanette Fabray Master Score, Conductor Score Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax Trumpets (1 thru 4) Trombones (1 thru 4) Violin (3 copies + addl. part) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Percussion Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 301 (Box Unknown container 474 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0108 (Box Unknown container 475 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Conductor Score (1 copy). Guests: Lucille Ball, Eddie Albert, Nancy Wilson. Artist: Eddie Albert. Parts: Alto Sax 1 Alto Sax 2 Tenor Sax 3 Tenor Sax 4 Baritone Sax Trumpets 1-4 TACIT Trombones 1-4 TACIT Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums TACIT Percussion (3 copies) Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 126 (Box Unknown container 476 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 477 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Guests: Don Rickles, Mel Torme, Nanette Fabray Artist: Nanette Fabray, Mel Torme Master Score, Conductor Score (1 copy) Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax 5th Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Percussion (3 copies) Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0118 (Box Unknown container 478 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0118 (Box Unknown container 479 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0118 (Box Unknown container 480 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0018 (Box Unknown container 481 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0114 (Box Unknown container 482 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 126 (Box Unknown container 483 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 126 (Box Unknown container 484 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 126 (Box Unknown container 485 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman (Box Unknown container 486 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 126 (Box Unknown container 487 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0121 (Box Unknown container 488 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0325 (Box Unknown container 489 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0121 (Box Unknown container 490 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0325 (Box Unknown container 491 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0324 (Box Unknown container 492 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0324 (Box Unknown container 493 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0324 (Box Unknown container 494 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0121 (Box Unknown container 495 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0121 (Box Unknown container 496 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0121 (Box Unknown container 497 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0121 (Box Unknown container 498 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0402 (Box Unknown container 499 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 500 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Conductor/Piano Score (2 copies). Guests: Don Rickles, Mel Torme, Nanette Fabray. Artist: Carol. Parts: Saxes, Trumpets, Trombones TACET Violins TACET Viola TACET Cello TACET Bass TACET Guitar TACET Percussion TACET Drums TACET Harp TACET
  - Harry Zimmerman, 126 (Box Unknown container 501 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0008 (Box Unknown container 502 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Production Score (orig. + 1 copy). Guests: Phyllis Diller, Gwen Verdon, Bobbie Gentry. Artist: Bobbie Gentry. Parts: Percussion (orig. + 2 copies) Violin (orig. + 4 copies) Harmonica 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0017 (Box Unknown container 503 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Conductor Score. Guests: Ella Fitzgerald, Sid Caesar. Artists: Carol Burnett, Ella Fitzgerald. Parts: Percussion (orig. + 3 copies) Violin (orig. + 3 copies) 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums Piano Harp
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0012 (Box Unknown container 504 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Guests: Richard Chamberlain, Gloria Loring. Parts: 3rd Bb Trumpet.
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0012 (Box Unknown container 505 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Production Score (orig. + 2 copies). Choir Lead Sheet (orig. + 5 copies). Guests: Richard Chamberlain, Gloria Loring. Parts: Percussion (orig. + 3 copies) Violin (orig. + 3 copies) 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0012 (Box Unknown container 506 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Production Score (orig. + copy). Lead Sheet; Choir Lead Sheet (orig. + 5 copies). Guests: Richard Chamberlain, Gloria Loring. Parts: Percussion (orig. + 2 copies) Violin (orig. + 3 copies) 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0010 (Box Unknown container 507 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Production Score (orig. + 2 copies). Guests: Jack Palance, Liza Minneli. Parts: Violin (orig. + 3 copies) 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax 5th Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Viola Cello Bass Guitar Percussion (orig.) Drums Harp Piano Carol Burnett Lead Sheet (orig.)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0010 (Box Unknown container 508 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Production Score (2 copies). Guests: Jack Palance, Liza Minneli. Artists: Carol, Liza Minneli. Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax 5th Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums Harp Piano Percussion (3 copies) Choir Lead Sheet (orig. + 1 copy)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0010 (Box Unknown container 509 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Production Score. Guests: Jack Palance, Liza Minneli. Artist: Jack Palance. Parts: Violin (orig. + 3 copies) Percussion (orig. + 1 copy) 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0010 (Box Unknown container 510 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Production Score. Guests: Jack Palance, Liza Minneli. Artists: Harvey Korman, Lyle Waggoner, Jack Palance. Parts: Violin (orig. + 3 copies) Percussion (orig. + 1 copies) 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0010 (Box Unknown container 511 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Production Score. Guests: Jack Palance, Liza Minneli. Parts: Saxes TACIT Trumpets TACIT Trombones TACIT Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar TACIT Percussion TACIT Drums TACIT Harp Piano TACIT
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0107 (Box Unknown container 512 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Conductor Score. Guests: Don Rickles, Mel Torme, Nanette Fabray. Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Violin (3 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Percussion Drums Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0008 (Box Unknown container 513 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Production Score (orig. + 1 copy). Guests: Phyllis Diller, Gwen Verdon, Bobbie Gentry. Artist: Gwen Verdon. Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Violin (4 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Percussion (3 copies) Drums Harp Piano Choir (orig.)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0002 (Box Unknown container 514 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 4 copies). Guests: Juliet Prowse, Martha Raye. Artist: Martha Raye. Parts: Eb Alto Sax 1 Eb Alto Sax 2 Bb Tenor Sax 1 Bb Tenor Sax 2 Baritone Sax Bb Trumpet 1 Bb Trumpet 2 Bb Trumpet 3 Bb Trumpet 4 Trombone 1 Trombone 2 Trombone 3 Trombone 4 Violin (4 copies) Viola Cello Bass Guitar Drums Percussion Harp Piano
  - Harry Zimmerman, 710 (Box Unknown container 515 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 710 (Box Unknown container 516 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 517 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 518 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 519 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Irwin Kostal, 814 (Box Unknown container 520 for instance of Irwin Kostal, Folder unknown container)
  - Irwin Kostal, 814 (Box Unknown container 521 for instance of Irwin Kostal, Folder unknown container)
  - Irwin Kostal, 814 (Box Unknown container 522 for instance of Irwin Kostal, Folder unknown container)
  - Irwin Kostal, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 523 for instance of Irwin Kostal, Folder unknown container)
  - J. Hill, 0410 (Box Unknown container 524 for instance of J. Hill, Folder unknown container)
  - J. Hill, Jimmie Rodgers Show No. 2 (Box Unknown container 525 for instance of J. Hill, Folder unknown container)
  - J. Hill, 308 (Box Unknown container 526 for instance of J. Hill, Folder unknown container)
    Master Score; Conductor Score. Guests: Bing Crosby, Ella Fitzgerald, Rowan & Martin. Artists: Bing Crosby. Parts: 1st Alto Sax 2nd Alto Sax 3rd Tenor Sax 4th Tenor Sax Baritone Sax 1st Trumpet 2nd Trumpet 3rd Trumpet 4th Trumpet 1st Trombone 2nd Trombone 3rd Trombone 4th Trombone Violin (3 copies) Cello Viola Bass Guitar Percussion (3 copies) Drums Harp Piano
  - J. Hill, 0419 (Box Unknown container 527 for instance of J. Hill, Folder unknown container)
  - J. Hill, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #5 (Box Unknown container 528 for instance of J. Hill, Folder unknown container)
  - J. Hill, None Listed (Box Unknown container 529 for instance of J. Hill, Folder unknown container)
  - J. Mele (Box Unknown container 530 for instance of J. Mele, Folder unknown container)
  - Joe Lipman, 0402 (Box Unknown container 531 for instance of Joe Lipman, Folder unknown container)
  - Joe Lipman (Box Unknown container 532 for instance of Joe Lipman, Folder unknown container)
  - Joe Lipman, 0325 (Box Unknown container 533 for instance of Joe Lipman, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 534 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 535 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson (Box Unknown container 536 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson (Box Unknown container 537 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 538 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 539 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 540 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson (Box Unknown container 541 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson, None Listed (Box Unknown container 542 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson (Box Unknown container 543 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson (Box Unknown container 544 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson (Box Unknown container 545 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson (Box Unknown container 546 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson (Box Unknown container 547 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson (Box Unknown container 548 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson (Box Unknown container 549 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Mort Garson (Box Unknown container 550 for instance of Mort Garson, Folder unknown container)
  - Nick Perito, 0514 (Box Unknown container 551 for instance of Nick Perito, Folder unknown container)
  - Nick Perito, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 552 for instance of Nick Perito, Folder unknown container)
  - None Listed, 0419 (Box Unknown container 553 for instance of None Listed, Folder unknown container)
  - None Listed, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 554 for instance of None Listed, Folder unknown container)
  - None Listed, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 555 for instance of None Listed, Folder unknown container)
  - Not Listed, 0002 (Box Unknown container 556 for instance of Not Listed, Folder unknown container)
    Guests: Juliet Prowse, Martha Raye. Parts: Cello TACIT
  - Not Listed, 0002 (Box Unknown container 557 for instance of Not Listed, Folder unknown container)
    Conductor Score. Guests: Juliet Prowse, Martha Raye.
  - Not Listed, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 558 for instance of Not Listed, Folder unknown container)
  - Not Listed, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 559 for instance of Not Listed, Folder unknown container)
  - Not Listed, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 560 for instance of Not Listed, Folder unknown container)
  - Not Listed, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 561 for instance of Not Listed, Folder unknown container)
  - Not Listed, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 562 for instance of Not Listed, Folder unknown container)
  - Not Listed, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 563 for instance of Not Listed, Folder unknown container)
  - Not Listed, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 564 for instance of Not Listed, Folder unknown container)
  - Not Stated, Julie and Carol at Lincoln Center (Box Unknown container 565 for instance of Not Stated, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, Carol + 2 (Box Unknown container 566 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 0513 (Box Unknown container 567 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 0512 (Box Unknown container 568 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 0512 (Box Unknown container 569 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 715 (Box Unknown container 570 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 715 (Box Unknown container 571 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 611 (Box Unknown container 572 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 622 (Box Unknown container 573 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 618 (Box Unknown container 574 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, C. Burnett Shows (Box Unknown container 575 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, C. Burnett Shows (Box Unknown container 576 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, C. Burnett Shows (Box Unknown container 577 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 620 (Box Unknown container 578 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 0014 (Box Unknown container 579 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 622 (Box Unknown container 580 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 622 (Box Unknown container 581 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 622 (Box Unknown container 582 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 622 (Box Unknown container 583 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 622 (Box Unknown container 584 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 622 (Box Unknown container 585 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 618 (Box Unknown container 586 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 620 (Box Unknown container 587 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)
  - Peter Matz, 0022 (Box Unknown container 588 for instance of Peter Matz, Folder unknown container)